I know you'll never be able to hide the
location of anything I mean mostly this
is just showing off how great it is to
work at koumei I still do perhaps the
greatest place in the world to work
that's right yeah to the comments in car
panties presentation yet I was gonna
watch it tonight oh yeah
when are you hiring a support person
when are we hiring a support person
yeah we're not yeah yeah well come here
a little bit far away
we can fix that I'm gonna park jealous
stop talking
are you having a support issue
no I do support so I need you to hire me
you're right we get it
well you open-source your semantic
segmentation no we'll show you the beach
am we clamped out the next year for
commentary
very good at asking the question now we
bought it with all the profit
this way like share their inner workings
very little transparency we have not
common at all
future the future many things be
discussed today yeah
they did all my questions what am i
doing all the primary
or you just get me on answers
let's go bees oh how is Honda Accord
support cats what they want to know no
hey no questions no speech what do we do
when they all offer level to agree well
we I mean that's the only place to go
right you guys know about the green
flash at sunset how is ford fusion
support going well bro I have bad news
for you know you know it's a joke
oh did you hear that I copy
was murder
all right good thing Isis bacon it's
emotional
stoplights are road map yes there's also
no way together
it is burgers my hobbies the flippin
anguish that is JoJo's I have it the
flippin they trying to pee outside
[Music]
it's all just to get people to think
about IHOP again no one's done that in
years
what about just add an executable to
Samantha secretary we don't ships member
we only ship fissioned it
when is it
oh yeah when dry on fire
how are you drinking for nugs you missed
us swimming we already went swimmin
we're gonna put the team picture up we
took a team photo on fire George hire
Wendy social media person I don't think
we have that kind of money guys not my
house you're too dumb to understand what
is grape and to do well white pandas are
white and gray pan is it gray yeah
they're different for a sec I had to
text my friend back
should I tell her we're on periscope she
wants to check it out
really what a lovely place
yeah me too
alright Skokie's we'll leave you with
full autonomy
Tesla fully autonomous by September guys
if that's true we'll closed out
accommodate don't worry about work I
never worry about where we're gonna live
ya know but if you are actually some
full self-driving like I can get my
tassel up by 4 I'm going to fall asleep
here we're gonna we're gonna take the
rest of the VC money by everyone who
works here Tess lager beer go for
it
[Applause]
no scope is alright
otherwise they wouldn't know if I jugged
it alright yeah oh you got you got a
pincher with your fingers yeah alright
so it's not full periscope is but I'll
see you later thank you for joining us
become AI off site give me a job at comm
a I'm gonna come work here
we're are only five people that's what
we decided you do I do I really do oh
can I ask me let all right later guys